okay today's video I don't know what I'm
saying
I don't know what the topic is because I
have about five minutes to record this
before I have to go pick my kid up from
school and no time between that and my
bedtime to do it at any other point but
last night I discovered a stream yard
and I really liked it I used it once to
go live on periscope it's just a
streaming app but I believe I can stream
on YouTube Facebook and periscope
simultaneously which got my wheels
turning last night laying in bed
supposed to be sleeping about creating
an idea I had a while ago of having an
hour booked for a I'm gonna say staff
meeting that's not right like a Board of
Directors meeting where we move this
project forward together and the people
that show up to do that will become the
board of directors and people who show
up consistently and once we have people
interested we're on video because I can
invite people and they can be on video
with me from their camera on this dream
yard which is also awesome because I
know that I can explain this much better
in a conversation in conversation
because I can see what doesn't make
sense and read and explain that piece of
it people ask questions and I can
respond to questions and so creating a
meeting or we're publicly talking about
how we're creating the global
cooperative whether it's with people
with disabilities or not we're creating
the hope cafe and there I will stand for
creating it so that it's as the ablest
as possible the opposite as accessible
as possible and just that excited I'm
excited to figure out this dreamer thing
and figure out it might be the one thing
I pay for but it's like 20 bucks a month
when you gets once it comes to the point
where I won't pay for that until I know
that I have hundred viewers regularly
and people are commenting and
interacting so that we can move forward
together in creating the technology that
we need to do everything we need to do
on this planet starting with what I'm
now calling the idea
Caffe instead of the hope cafe because
it has a different connotation when I'm
talking about working with people with
disabilities than it does Fergie anyway
than it does when we're talking about
global warming on the planet yes it's
just it's a different connotation so and
it's what we're gonna be talking about
is our ideas our thoughts and creating
the space to have a global conversation
a real global conversation where you
will be given people to talk to you do
not need to be an expert just bring who
you are and be part of the conversation
and I'm gonna showcase that with us
being on camera and having conversations
with people that care about the issues
and then moving forward with right now
how do we get even more people involved
and that will be doing the idea cafe on
Zoom and Facebook people joining in
saying when they're available and then
setting up time periods within a week
and then once we get even more people we
can possibly move to daily which is what
the idea in cafe will be it'll be a new
question every day that people can
participate in or not participate in and
people will be assigned people to talk
to you and they can talk for one slot or
no slots or as many slots as they want
and the more slots you talk to the more
individual conversations you are having
and the more you'll be able to
contribute to finding the thread that
runs through that but there'll only be
some people who find the thread some
people who experience different
conversations and then the next
conversation they have on the next day
can be about what did you find in common
and we can create ways to to what the
world cafe calls harvest those ideas
find a way to visualize them and move
forward with them when the world is able
to connect and have a conversation a
real powerful conversation even if
nothing comes of that directly even if
we'd never create another thing that in
and of itself is powerful enough because
when we can see each other when we
connect with each other it's a lot
harder to other us to create false
truths about other groups of people and
the more we can honor us all as
individuals without requiring anybody be
anyone but who they currently are
capable of being how do you know they're
only curled leap capable of being who
they are because that's who they are if
they were capable of being somebody
different
be somebody different and love and
acceptance of people who and as they are
has so much power and beauty in it it is
how we help people evolve and grow and
by loving them for exactly as they are
and yet we never have to deal with
someone else's we'd never have
to like continually sit with somebody
again and again if they if they trigger
us and offend us but we don't get to say
they don't get to be at the at a table
and at a conversation and I feel like
I've talked for five minutes
I don't know if I've said anything
important but I'm gonna re-watch this
again later create a title and post it
before I go to bed tonight
so a better world is on its way it's
gonna be brought to you by our diversity
all our diversity it is going to be
simple and enjoyable for every
individual to contribute and
collectively we are gonna create
amazingness please like and subscribe
and hit that little bell and I'll see
you tomorrow